

### **CONTACT ME**

501 297 401

mar.bogucki@gmail.com

https://marbogucki.github.io/

in) marcin-bogucki-a96a8672

### LANGUAGES

O English - B1

#### **HOBBIES**

- Nutrition & Cooking
- Board games
- ⊙ Sport gym, volleyball
- ⊙ Job-related Literature

# Marcin Bogucki

Front-end Developer, Web Designer

A demanding job as a Front-end Developer will enable me to combine both my knowledge and practical skills. Willing to be a member of a professional team to improve job-related skills while gaining working experience, especially JavaScript / Ecma Script 6, React JS.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2017-01 / today 1 year 5 mths (Gdansk)

LPI

Front-end Developer

Websites: Reserved, Mohito, Sinsay, Cropp, House

2014-03 / 2016-12 2 years 10 mths (Pruszkow) DaVinci Medical System

Web Designer

Interfaces web application, preparation of HTML and CSS code for medical applications

2013-04 / 2014-03 1 year (Gdansk) Etendard Sp. zo.o.

Junior Front-end Developer

Website, online shops and web application (HTML adn CSS template creation)

2010-10 / 2013-03 2 years 6 mths (Warsaw) Grupa Wsparcia Projektów Inwestycyjnych

Web Designer

Website design and building templates (HTML and CSS)

2008-09/ 2012-09 4 years 1 mth (Warsaw) **Education Media House**WebDesigner

Creating templates electronic diary for schools

### **EDUCATION**

2016	0	info Share Academy Front-end Developer Training
2014	0	<b>Eduweb</b> Responsive Web Design
2006-2007	0	Post-secondary school TEB Edukacja Graphic Designer
2005-2008	0	University of Warmia and Mazury in Olsztyn  Course in teaching and methodology, IT training qualifications
2003-2008	0	University of Warmia and Mazury in Olsztyn MSc Technical-Information Education

## (\>) SKILLS



I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.